

annielee1993@gmail.com | (213) 807-4317 | Gainesville, VA 20155

Summary

Highly-motivated U.S. Army Veteran seeking employment within the federal/local government. Attentive individual who brings strong background in providing trainings, conducting research, and advising administrative and management support. Committed to giving positive customer service with strong problem solving abilities. Extensive experience in delivering expert training, briefings, and presentation to various sizes of groups. Adept at working effectively unsupervised and quickly mastering new skills. Reliable and detail-focused individual offering 5 years of superior staff support, including projects management, event planning and coordination, and expert communication skills.

Skills

- Organizational Leadership
- Personnel/Staff Management
- Project/ Program Development
- Research and Publication
- Presentation and Briefing

- Interpersonal and Written Communication
- Event Coordination
- Confidential Document Control
- Proficient with Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and Teams

Special Hiring Authority

• Veteran Preference

Federal Experience

• Military- U.S. Army

Clearance

• Qualified for T5

Experience

Walter Reed Army Institute of Research (WRAIR)- US Army | Silver Spring, MD BEHAVIORAL HEALTH TECHNICIAN 02/2019 - 02/2024

- Managed quality control for 48,000 Soldier surveys for the Readiness and Suicide Risk Reduction Review Study spearheaded by the Deputy Under Secretary of the Army
- Recruited over 100+ participants via various recruitment systems and administered clinical research within the Military Psychiatry Branch
- Reviewed and evaluated research protocols and procedures using analytical skills within the WRAIR Human Subject Protection Branch as an Institutional Review Board (IRB) member
- Cooperated in the making of thesis and poster presentation for the Military Health System Research Symposium
- As a Research Assistant, worked over 40-45 hours per week to quality control and assure urgent data for the military research within Military Psychiatry Branch
- Gathered and collected data from multiple military bases including Fort

Carson, Fort Jackson, Fort Leavenworth, Fort Bliss, and more

- Adhered to all HIPAA regulations regarding confidentiality and privacy when handling sensitive information about clients' personal information
- Managed and accountable of training for 4 Officers, 4 Enlisted Soldiers, 6 Civilian Scientists, and 4 Research Assistants
- Engaged with multidisciplinary teams such as psychiatrists, psychologists, social workers, and medical doctors to support and improve the military research and its application.

Glenoaks Christian Private School | San Fernando, CA **DAY CARE ADVISOR** 08/2016 - 04/2017

- Managed an after-school program to help children with their homework, understand their assignments didactically
- Collaborated with external organizations to provide holistic services for the children with special assistance
- Adhered to established ethical standards when dealing with sensitive information or difficult situations
- Utilized organizational skills to manage numerous cases simultaneously, ensuring all children and parents' requests were addressed promptly
- Applied and practiced effective customer service with parents, families, and teachers through professional communication.
- Provided administrative support for the school staff with attendance reports and parent-teacher correspondence.
- Troubleshot and resolved complex customer service issues to enhance school staff and family experience.

Ivy Rehab for Kids | Gainesville, VA OCCUPATIONAL THERAPIST AIDE 04/2023 - 05/2023

- Monitored treatment effectiveness at different stages, adjusting to achieve maximum benefit
- Maintained accurate records of treatments provided to ensure continuity of care across multiple providers
- Provided emotional support and encouragement throughout the course of treatment
- Assisted with equipment set up for therapeutic exercises.

Fort Belvoir Community Hospital Springfield, VA OCCUPATIONAL THERAPY INTERN 02/2023 - 03/2023

- Collaborated with physicians and other healthcare providers regarding changes in patient condition or goals for therapy intervention
- Evaluated functional limitations due to injury or illness then implemented appropriate strategies for improvement
- Established positive relationships with clients through effective communication and active listening skills
- Evaluated patients' progress and prepared reports that detail progress.

Education and Training

University of California, Riverside | Riverside, CA **Bachelor of Arts** in Public Policy 06/2016

- Member of Pi Beta Phi, 2015-2016
- Vice President Chair of The Leadership Community for Women, 2015-2016

Northern Virginia Community College | Annandale, VA Some College (No Degree)

- Completed Abnormal Psychology and Developmental Psychology Courses
- 4.0 GPA

Montgomery College | Rockville, MD

Some College (No Degree)

- Completed Medical Terminology Course
- 4.0 GPA

Certifications

- Basic Life Support/ Basic Life Support Instructor, American Red Cross, 2022
- Defense Language Proficiency in Korean, US Army, 2022
- HIPAA Certification, Defense Health Agency, 2023

Languages

Korean:

Native/ Bilingual

Accomplishments

- Army Commendation Medal
- Army Achievement Medal